const DATA = { 
    // multiple and binary questions
    "questions": [
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `rtyrt`,
            ans3: `try`,
            ans4: `yrtyr`,
            correctAns: `ans1`
        },
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `rtyrt`,
            ans3: `try`,
            ans4: `yrtyr`,
            correctAns: `ans1`
        },
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `כעגעכ`,
            ans2: `rtyrt`,
            ans3: `try`,
            ans4: `נכון`,
            correctAns: `ans4`
        },
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `עכגע`,
            ans2: `rtyrt`,
            ans3: `נכון`,
            ans4: `yrtyr`,
            correctAns: `ans3`
        },
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `כרכע`,
            ans2: `rtyrt`,
            ans3: `נכון`,
            ans4: `דלכדגךףכ`,
            correctAns: `ans3`
        },
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `כקכ`,
            ans2: `נכון`,
            ans3: `try`,
            ans4: `yrtyr`,
            correctAns: `ans2`
        },
        {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה וגם בלה`,
            ans1: `ןח'ךלגכ`,
            ans2: `נכון`,
            ans3: `try`,
            ans4: `yrtyr`,
            correctAns: `ans2`
        },
        {
            type: `binary`,
            question: `uyt`,
            correctAns: true
        },
        {
            type: `binary`,
            question: `לא נכון`,
            correctAns: false
        },
        {
            type: `binary`,
            question: `uyt`,
            correctAns: true
        },
    ],
    // complete the sentence
    "completeSentence": [
        
        
    ]
};